Delaney, James Joseph; Papers apap241
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Legislative Files, 1950-1978, 1; 9.65 cubic ft.
  - Subject Files; Arranged Chronologically, 1950-1978; 1.3
    - H.R. 8543, Gateway National Recreation Area, 92nd, 1971 May (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 55)
    - H. Res. 465, Rule on H.R. 8293 (International Coffee Agreement), 92nd, 1971 June (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 56)
    - H. Res. 558, Select Supreme Court Study Committee, 92nd, 1971 July (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 57)
    - H.R. 10741, To Authorize the Secretary of the Interior to Establish the Gardiners Island National Monument, 92nd, 1971 September (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 58)
    - H. Res. 635, Irish Resolution, 92nd. Includes correspondence, 1971 October (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 59)
    - H. Res. 663, F-4 Aircrafts to Israel, 92nd. Includes correspondence Gerald Ford, 1971 October (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 60)
    - H.R. 11248, Prescription Drugs Under Medicare, 92nd, 1971 October (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 61)
    - H.R. 11690, National Marine Mineral Resource Trust, 92nd, 1971 October (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 62)
    - Correspondence, H.J. Res. 949, Appreciate America Day, 1971 November (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 63)
    - H.R. 1257, Coastal Hazards in the Atlantic Ocean, 92nd, 1971 December (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 64)
    - H.R. 12207, Deportation of Aliens on Welfare, 92nd, 1971 December (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 65)
    - H.R. 12160, Northern Irish Relief Act of 1971, 92nd, 1971 December (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 66)
    - H.R. 12477, Directing FCC to Investigate AT&T, 92nd, 1972 January 19 (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 67)
    - H.R. 334, 450, 16555, 12690, January 1972-1975 H.R. 334, Tuition Tax Credit for Private Non Profit Schools, 94th, January 1975, H.R. 450, Tuition Tax Credit, 93rd, January 1973, H.R. 16555, Tuition Tax Credit, 92nd, September 1972, H.R. 12690, Tax Credit for Non Public School Tuition, 92nd, January 1972 (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 68)
    - H.R. 13224, Protect Diplomatic Mission in NY, 92nd, 1972 February (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 69)
    - H.R. 12802, Maritime Academy Students as Navy Reserve Shipmen, 92nd, 1972 February (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 70)
    - H. Con. Res. 555, Ukrainian Churches, 92nd, 1972 March (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 71)
    - H.R. 6486, Clean Lakes Act, 92nd. Includes S. 1017, 1972 March (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 72)
    - H. Con. Res. 13684, Urban Mass Transit Assistance, 92nd, 1972 March (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 73)
    - H.R. 13963, Aircraft Crimes. See H.R. 1256, 1972 March (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 74)
    - H. Res. 864, 1266, 14586, 11482, 7440, April 1972-May 1973 H. Res. 864, Informal House Textile Committee Resolution, 95th, October 1977, H.R. 1266, Establish Office of Consumer Affairs, 94th, January 1975, H.R. 14586, To Provide for the Prevention of Cooley’s Anemia, 92nd, April 1972, H.R. 11482, Establish Day Lights Savings Time Year Round, November 1973, H.R. 7440, To Expand the Authority of National Institute of Arthritis, 93rd, May 1973, 1972 April-1973 May (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 75)
    - H.R. 15193, Retarded Children Education, 92nd, 1972 May (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 76)
    - H.R. 15734, Bill of Rights for Mentally Retarded, 92nd, 1972 June (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 77)
    - H.R. 15776, Training Ship for Board of Education, 92nd, 1972 June (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 78)
    - H. Con. Res. 663, Prisoners of War, 92nd, 1972 August (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 79)
    - H. Res. 1085, Rule For Consideration of H.R. 15927, Increase Rail Road Retirement Annuities, 92nd, 1972 August (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 80)
    - H.R. 16381, Council on Energy Policy, 92nd, 1972 August (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 81)
    - H.R. 17072, 16555, Public and Private Education Assistance, 92nd Congress, 1972 August-1972 October (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 82)
    - H. Con. Res. 697, Condemn Soviets for Ransoming Jews, 92nd, 1972 September (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 83)
    - H. Res. 1135, Rule on H.R. 1121 (Gateway Sea Shore), 92nd, 1972 September (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 84)
    - H.R. 16682, Highway Trust Funds of Urban Transportation, 92nd, 1972 September (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 85)
    - H.R. 1418, 16533, 15130, 342, September 1972-1975 H.R. 1418, To Eliminate Social Security Earnings Limitation, 93rd, November 1973, H.R. 16533, To Assure Social Security Increase for Aged, Disabled, Etc., 92nd September 1972, H.R. 15130, SSI Reform Bill, 93rd, May 1974, H.R. 342, Eliminate the Earnings Test for Social Security, January 1975 (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 86)
    - H. Res. 1151, Polish Constitution Day, 92nd, 1972 October (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 87)
    - H.R. 446, Tuition Voucher Proposals, 93rd, 1973 January (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 1)
    - H.J. Res. 290, 261, Anti Abortion-To Protect the Unborn, the Aged, and the Incapacitated, 93rd, 1973 February (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 2)
    - H.R. 5590, Fire Research and Training, 93rd, 1973 March (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 3)
    - H.R. 5708, Right of Conscience in Abortion Procedures Act, 93rd, 1973 March (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 4)
    - H.R. 6008, To Amend the Economic Stabilization Act, 93rd, 1973 March (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 5)
    - H.R. 9541, 5755, 14590, H. Res. 803 H.R. 9541, Mass Transit Use Income Tax Deduction, 94th, September 1975, H.R. 5755, To Suspend Importation of Liquefied Natural Gas, 93rd, March 1973, H.R. 14590, Auto Insurance Foreign Resident (NY), 94th, June 1976. H. Res. 803, Protest U.N. Statement Re: Zionism, 94th, October 1975, 1973 March-1976 June (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 6)
    - H.R. 6786, Research Institute for Dysautonomia, 93rd, 1973 April (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 7)
    - H.R. 9016, Hurricane Flood Protection and Beach Erosion Control at East Rockaway Inlet to Rockaway Inlet and Jamaica Bay, New York, 93rd, 1973 June (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 8)
    - H.R. 8739, NY Harbor Collection and Removal of Drift, 93rd, 1973 June (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 9)
    - H.R. 10020, Federal Funds to Provide Police Protection for 25th Anniversary of United Nations, 93rd, 1973 August (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 10)
    - H.R. 10211 Vitamin + Mineral Supplement Bill, 93rd, 1973 September (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 11)
    - H.R. 10831/10844, To Amend the Export Administration Act, 93rd, 1973 October (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 12)
    - H. Con. Res. 719, H. Res. 1484, H.R. 11920, H. Con. Res. 719, Place North Korean Armistice Violations before U.N., 94th, August 1976, H. Res. 1484, Condemn Treacherous Acts of North Korea and Extend Condolences to Families of 2 slain G.I.’s, 94th, August 1976, H.R. 11920, To Require Food Labels to Disclose All Ingredients, 93rd, December 1973, 1973 December-1976 August (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 13)
    - H. R. 9652, 13190, H.R. 9652, Uniform Federal Welfare and Medicaid Assistance Act of 1975, 94th, September 1975, H.R. 13190, Federal Participation in Costs of Social Security Program, Increase Contributions, 93rd, March 1974, 1974 March-1975 September (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 14)
    - H. Res. 1120, To Condemn Terrorist killings of Israeli Children, 93rd, 1974 May (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 15)
    - H.R. 16202, To Establish in the Department of HUD a Housing Enforcement Assistance Program to aid Cities and Municipalities in the More effective Enforcement of Housing Codes, 93rd, 1974 July (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 16)
    - H. Res. 540, Panama Canal, 92nd, 1974 July (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 17)
    - H. Con. Res. 649, Ukrainian Intellectuals Moroz, Valentyn & Plyushch, Leonid, 1974 September (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 18)
    - H.R. 17492, Tax Exempt, the First $500 of Interest Earned in Certain Savings Institutions, 93rd, 1974 November (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 19)
    - H.R. 330, 325, 2292, 321, 323, 1263, 1266, 328, 331, 332, 94th, H.R. 330, Oil Imports no U.S. Flag Vessels, H.R. 325, Deportation of Aliens on Welfare, H.R. 2292, Prohibits Employment of Illegal Aliens, H.R. 321, Curb Narcotics Traffic, H.R. 323, Vitamin Bill, H.R. 1263, Prohibit Federal Funds for Research on Human Fetus, H.R. 1266, Establish Office of Consumer Affairs, H.R. 328, Prohibit Cigarette Smuggling, H.R. 331, Veteran’s Pension Benefits, H.R. 332, NY Harbor Removal of Drift, 1975 January (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 20)
    - H.R. 3470, 12598, 751, 763, 1077, Education Tax Bill, 93rd-94th, 1975 January-1976 March (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 21)
    - H. Con. Res. 159, Soviet Occupation of Baltic Nations, 94th, 1975 February (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 22)
    - H.R. 3968, Release Impounded Highway Trust Funds, 94th Congress, 1975 February (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 23)
    - H.R. 4888, Small Business Loans, 94th, 1975 March (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 24)
    - H.R. 5483, Hudson River Compact Commission, 94th, 1975 March (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 25)
    - H. Res. 74091, Illegal Aliens, 94th, 1975 May (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 26)
    - H. Con. Res. 315, 41,221, Ukrainian Intellectuals Moroz, Valentyn & Plyushch, Leonid, 1975 June (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 27)
    - H.R. 9096, Vitamin Bill (Update of H.R. 323), 94th, 1975 July (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 28)
    - H.R. 10435, 15733, Prohibit NYC Bridge Tolls Order by EPA, 94th, 1975 October (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 29)
    - H. Res. 830, Honoring Bob Hope, 94th, 1975 October (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 30)
    - H. Con. Res. 472, Baltic Resolution, 94th, 1975 November (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 31)
    - H.R. 10600, Young Adult Conservation Corp, November 1974, 94th, 1975 November (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 32)
    - H. Res. 865, Rule on H.R. 10481 (NYC Bill), 94th, 1975 November (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, Fur Conservation Institute of America, 1975 November (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 34)
    - H. Res. 902, 907, 94th. H. Res. 902 Rule on S. 95 (Overseas Voting Rights), H. Res. 907, Panama Canal, 1975 December (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 35)
    - H. Con. Res. 550, Second Brussels Conference, 94th, 1976 February (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 36)
    - H. J. Res. 900, Thomas Jefferson Day, 94th, 1976 April (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 37)
    - H. Res. 1168, Solidarity Sunday, 94th, 1976 April (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 38)
    - H.R. 13490, 1980 Olympic Winter Games, 94th, 1976 April (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 39)
    - H. Con. Res. 637, Ukrainian Intellectual Moroz, Valentyn, 94th, 1976 May (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 40)
    - H.R. 13900, Rehabilitation, Act Amendments, 94th, 1976 May (Box 12 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 41)
    - H. Res. 1281, 1308, 1350, 1293, 94th, H. Res. 1281, Hearings on the Future of Telecommunication Policy of the Nation, H. Res. 1308, Closing of Post Offices, H. Res. 1350, Select Committee on Narcotics Abuse and Control, H. Res. 1293, Soviet Jews- Package Restrictions, 1976 June (Box 13 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 1)
    - H.R.14509, Senior Citizen Lease Termination, 94th, 1976 June (Box 13 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 2)
    - H.R. 15683, Restrictions on Diplomatic Immunity for Foreign Embassy Personnel, 94th, 1976 September (Box 13 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 3)
    - H.R. 15804, Bridge Safety Act of 1976, 94th, 1976 September (Box 13 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 4)
    - H.R. 15838, Federal Matching Funds for Tree Planting and Preservation, 94th, 1976 October (Box 13 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 5)
    - H.R. 2639, 30, 181, 327, 331, 333, 337, 821, 1474, 1477, 2701, 2640 95th. H.R. 2639,Extended Public Works Employment Act, Counter Cyclical Aid, H.R. 30, Young Adult Conservation Corps, H.R. 181, Law Enforcement Officers’ Bill of Rights, H.R. 327, Truth in Food Labeling Act, H.R. 331, Prohibit Cigarette Smuggling, H.R. 333, To Amend Title II of The Social Security Act, H.R. 337, Uniform Welfare and Medicaid Assistance Act of 1977, H.R. 821, Middle Aged and Older Workers Training Act of 1977, H.R. 1474, Deportation of Aliens on Welfare, H.R. 1477, Social Security Coverage for Federal Employees,. H.R. 2701, Restriction on Diplomatic Immunity, 2640, Economic Development Revenue Bond Act, 1977 January (Box 13 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 6)
    - H. Res. 36, 213, 28, 95th, H.Res.36, Solidarity Sunday with Jews, H. Res. 213, President’s Policy on a Nuclear Test Ban, H. Res. 28, Persecution of Hungarians in Romania, 1977 January (Box 13 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 7)
    - H. Con. Res. 12, The release of Ukrainian Intellectual Moroz, Valentyn, 95th, 1977 January (Box 13 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 8)
    - H. J. Res. 271, 1071, National Volunteer Firemen Week, 95th, 1977 February (Box 13 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 9)
    - H.R. 2853, 2938, 3003, 95th, H.R. 2853, Federal Matching Funds for Tree Planting and Preservation, H.R. 2938, Extend EPA Deadline for Water Pollution Control Funds, H.R. 3003, National Meals on Wheels Program, 1977 February (Box 13 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 10)
    - H.R. 3146, 3907, 4121, 4135, 95th, H.R. 3146, Medicare Coverage for Prescription Drugs (Outpatient), 95th Congress, H.R. 3907, Bridge Safety Act of 1977, H.R. 4121, Allow Workers Covered by Pension Plan to Invest in an IRA, H.R. 4135, Prohibit NYC Bridge Tolls Order By EPA., 1977 February (Box 13 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 11)
    - H.R. 4237, to designate the Veterans Administration Hospital at St. Albans as the “Henry Schuman Veterans Hospital”, 95th Congress, 1977 March (Box 13 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 12)
    - H.R. 5616 Accelerated Depreciation Allowance Act of 1977, 95th Congress, 1977 March (Box 13 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 13)
    - H. Con. Res. 165, Ukrainian Churches, 95th Congress, 1977 March (Box 13 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 14)
    - H. Con. Res. 174, Dr. Sergei Kovalev, 95th Congress, 1977 March (Box 13 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 15)
    - H.R. 5414, Supplemental Appropriation: Home Health Service and Multi Purpose Senior Centers, 95th, 1977 March (Box 13 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 16)
    - H.R. 6423, Volunteer Firemen- Exemption from Excise Taxes, 95th, 1977 April (Box 13 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 17)
    - H. J. Res. 409, National Grandparents Day, 95th, 1977 April (Box 13 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 18)
    - H. J. Res. 458, National Gifted and Talented Children’s Week, 95th Congress, 1977 May (Box 13 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 19)
    - H.R. 766, Reform of the Administrative, Organization and Legislative Management Services of the House, 95th, 1977 September (Box 13 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, Obey Commission- House Administration, 1977 September (Box 13 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 21-22)
    - H.R. 10974, 12546, 9035, 9492, 7488, 95th. H.R. 7488, Toll Free Calling, 1977 September-1978 (Box 13 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 23)
- Communications, 1956-1978; 2; 2 cubic ft.
  The folders in this series are arranged chronologically and include speeches, statements, press releases and other communication between Delaney’s office and the media. Folders with H.R. jackets include correspondence and Delaney’s notes. Topics of statements and press releases include abortion, social security, and the international drug trade.
  - Federal Aid to Education, H.R. 1 –Welfare Reform, Tuition Tax Credit to Ways and Means, Statements 91st-95th Congress Release and Statements, Undated (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 1)
  - [Federal Aid to Education?], Press Releases and Statements, 1955-1962 (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 2)
  - Federal Aid to Education, Power Memorial Academy, New York, Statement, 1956 February (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 3)
  - Committee on Food Additive Bill, Statement, 1957 March (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 4)
  - Chemicals in Our Food can Cause Cancer (Aramite Chemical Speech), Statement, 1958 April (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 5)
  - Food Additives, Statement, 1958 April-1958 October (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 6)
  - Delaney in Opposition to use of Citrus Red NO2 for Coloring Oranges, Statement, 1959 March (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 7)
  - Food Additives, Statements, 1960-1961 (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 8)
  - Food Additives Amendment of 1958, Statement, 1961 February-1961 March (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 9)
  - Citizens for Educational Reform, Statement, 1961 March (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 10)
  - Federal Aid to Education Statement, 1961 August (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 11)
  - Disadvantaged Poor: Education and Employment-Chamber of Commence, Release, 1962 January (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 12)
  - “School Children Assistance Act”, Federation of Italian American Democratic Organization, Statement, 1962 January (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 13)
  - Federal Aid to Education, Catholic Lawyers Guild, New York, Catholic Associates of NYLIC Catholic War Veterans, Statement, 1962 February-1962 May (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 14)
  - Spellman, Cardinal, Release and Statement, 1962 May-1962 August (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 15)
  - Ribicoff, Abraham, Statement, 1963 May (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 16)
  - Delaney on Education (General), Statement, 1963 (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 17)
  - Reverend Drinan, Robert, Statement, 1963 January (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 18)
  - The National Education Improvement Act of 1963, Statement by others, 1963 January-1963 June (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 19-20)
  - Drug Control Act of 1964, Release and Statement, 1963 June (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 21)
  - Cosmetics and consumer protection Release and Statement, 1963 August (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 22)
  - Higher Education Facilities Act of 1963, Statement, Delaney and others, 1963 October (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 23)
  - Federal Aid to Education, Statement, 1963 October (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 24)
  - Joint Hearings on Fluoridation City of New York, Statement, 1963 November (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 25)
  - President Johnson, Lyndon B., Press Release, 1964 January (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 26)
  - Fuller, Edgar, Statement, 1964 February (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 27)
  - Whelan, Charles M., Statement, 1964 February (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 28)
  - Zirkel, Don, Statement, 1964 April (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 29)
  - Keppel, Francis, Statement, 1964 July (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 30)
  - Democratic National Convention, Statement, 1964 August (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 31)
  - Drug Abuse Control Amendments, Release, 1965 February (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 32)
  - Statement, 1965 February-1965 March (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 33)
  - Statement, 1966 February-1966 March (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 34)
  - New York City Firemen, Statement, 1966 April (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 35)
  - Delores Cook, Eulogy, 1969 May (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 36)
  - Chemicals in Foods, Release, 1969 August (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 37)
  - School Children’s Assistant Act, Statement Delaney and others, 1969 October-1969 November (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 38)
  - Delaney and Others, G.I. Bill, Statement, 1969 November-1969 December (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 39-40)
  - FDA and Cyclamates, Statement, 1970 June (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 41)
  - Ukrainian Independence, Voucher Plan H.R. 128, Mercury Pollution, Tribute to Speaker McCormack, Statement, 1971 January (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 42)
  - Rockefeller’s Support of Non Public School Aid, Reply to Attacks on Vouchers, Cancer Agency Bill, Statement, 1971 February (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 43)
  - Byelorussian Independence, National Week of Concern for POW/MIAs, Senator Buckley Dinner, Statement, 1971 March (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 44)
  - Happy Birthday Farley, Jim, Romanian Independence Day, Statement, 1971 May (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 45)
  - Senator Dodd, Thomas J., Eulogy, 1971 June (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 46)
  - Interview with Farley, James A., 1971 June (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 47)
  - Illegal International Trade in Drugs, Reimbursement to NYC for U.N., Opening of the Astoria Social Security Office, Halting of Seal Killing, Statement, 1971 July (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 48)
  - Statements, 1971 September (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 49)
  - 15th Anniversary of the Hungarian Revolution, Expulsion of the Republic of China from the U.N., Illegal Aliens, North Ireland, Honorable Farley, James A., Asking American People to Boycott French Products until Drug Traffic from Marseilles is eliminated, Statement, 1971 October (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 50)
  - St. Alban’s Naval Hospital, Statement, 1971 November (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 51)
  - Christianson, Curtis, Statement, 1971 December (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 52)
  - Duffy, Thomas in Belfast, To Demand Release of American Citizen Held in North Ireland, To Create a Joint Committee to Study Problems, Release, 1971 December (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 53)
  - Farley, Jim, Insertion, 1972 January (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 54)
  - Social Security, Telephone Rates Release, 1972 January (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 55)
  - Blood Banks, Anti Smut Day, Ukrainian Independence, Queens Chamber of Commerce, Tuition Voucher, Statement, 1972 January (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 56)
  - Social Security Increase, Visa for Resident of Northern Ireland, Chemicals Guilty Until Proven Innocent, Bulova Watch Statement, Chemicals Cyclamates, Saccharin and Animal Feeds, Statement, 1972 February (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 57)
  - Honorable Forand, Aime J., Eulogy, 1972 February (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 58)
  - Letter to the President on Voucher Proposal, Stilbestrol DES, Release, 1972 February (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 59)
  - Congressman Timble, Eulogy, 1972 March (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 60)
  - Extension of Remarks, Senator Buckley, 1972 March (Box 14 (2-Communications), Folder 61)